export default [
  {
    question: 'A carrot is a(n)...',
    answers: [
      'vegetable',
      'fruit',
      'sport',
      'animal',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'vegetable',
  },
  {
    question: 'green is a(n)...',
    answers: [
      'instrument',
      'fruit',
      'color',
      'animal',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'color',
  },
  {
    question: 'apples are a(n)...',
    answers: [
      'animal',
      'vegetable',
      'fruit',
      'accessory',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'fruit',
  },
  {
    question: 'football is a(n)...',
    answers: [
      'vegetable',
      'sport',
      'fruit',
      'animal',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'sport',
  },
  {
    question: 'The word beautiful is a(n)...',
    answers: [
      'insult',
      'fruit',
      'compliment',
      'animal',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'compliment',
  },
  {
    question: 'A phone is a(n)...',
    answers: [
      'electronic device',
      'fruit',
      'sport',
      'animal',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'electronic device',
  },
  {
    question: 'A shirt is a(n)...',
    answers: [
      'vegetable',
      'type of phone',
      'sport',
      'piece of clothing',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'piece of clothing',
  },
  {
    question: 'shoes belong on',
    answers: [
      'your hands',
      'your feet',
      'your chest',
      'your bottom',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'your feet',
  },
  {
    question: 'Monday is a(an)',
    answers: [
      'day of the week',
      'food item',
      'piece of clothing',
      'animal',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'day of the week',
  },
  {
    question: 'a hat belongs on',
    answers: [
      'your face',
      'your hand',
      'your head',
      'your bottom',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'your head',
  },
];
